[
  {
    "id": "001",
    "Question": "How many warehouses does ShipCube have worldwide?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently operates six warehouses worldwide — four in the United States and two in the United Arab Emirates — with additional locations planned for the future.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "002",
    "Question": "How many warehouses does ShipCube have in India?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently does not have any warehouses in India.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "003",
    "Question": "What is shipcube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube is a leading global warehousing and logistics service provider, offering reliable and efficient storage and distribution solutions worldwide.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "004",
    "Question": "What services does ShipCube provide?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube provides a range of services including Third-Party Logistics (3PL), Strategic Warehousing Facilities, and Logistics Hub Management Centers.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "005",
    "Question": "What types of fulfillment services does ShipCube handle?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube handles various types of fulfillment services, including Direct-to-Consumer (DTC) Fulfillment, Business-to-Business (B2B) Fulfillment, and Amazon FBA Prep Fulfillment. \"",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "006",
    "Question": "Which platforms do you use to integrate with your storefront?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube integrates seamlessly with multiple e-commerce platforms, including Amazon, Zoho, Shopify, BigCommerce, WooCommerce, Magento 2, TikTok Shop, and OpenCart.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "007",
    "Question": "What is the address of shipcube?",
    "Answer": "The address of ShipCube is 2894 South Orange Avenue, Fresno, California 93725, USA.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "008",
    "Question": "What is the telephone number of ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "You can call us at +1 (559) 931-3893",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "009",
    "Question": "What is the official email address of ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The official email address of ShipCube is hello@shipcube.com.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "010",
    "Question": "What service you provide to say goodbye to logistics worries?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube offers comprehensive solutions including Delivery, Fulfillment, Seamless Integration, Dedicated Account Management, Real-Time Inventory Tracking, Kitting & Assembly, and Order Tracking — ensuring a smooth and efficient logistics experience. \"",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "011",
    "Question": "In which cities are ShipCube’s warehouses located?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's warehouses are located in New Jersey, Pennsylvania, California, Texas, and the United Arab Emirates (UAE).",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "012",
    "Question": "How many customers does ShipCube have?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube proudly serves over 100,000 customers worldwide, providing reliable and efficient logistics and fulfillment solutions.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "013",
    "Question": "How many courier partners does ShipCube have?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube has partnerships with over 20 leading courier companies to ensure fast and reliable global deliveries.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "014",
    "Question": "How many fulfillment centers does ShipCube have?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube operates 7 advanced fulfillment centers strategically located to ensure efficient global order processing and delivery.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "015",
    "Question": "Who is the Founder of shipcube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube was founded by Hooner Baweja.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "016",
    "Question": "Who is the CEO of shipcube?",
    "Answer": "The CEO of ShipCube is Hooner Baweja.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "017",
    "Question": "Can I speak with a ShipCube expert for more information or assistance?",
    "Answer": "You can contact a ShipCube expert by emailing hello@shipcube.com or visiting their official website to connect with the support team for professional assistance.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "018",
    "Question": "How much time does it take to connect with a ShipCube expert?",
    "Answer": "You can connect with a ShipCube expert for 30 minutes for assistance or consultation.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "019",
    "Question": "Can I schedule the meeting time according to my own time zone or preference?",
    "Answer": "Yes, you can schedule the meeting at a time that suits your time zone and availability.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "020",
    "Question": "How much time does the website take to book an appointment?",
    "Answer": "The website takes only 1 minute to book an appointment.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "021",
    "Question": "In which year was ShipCube founded?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube was founded in the year 2020.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "022",
    "Question": "How many werehouses shipcube operate in USA?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently operates four state-of-the-art warehouses across the United States.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "023",
    "Question": "How many werehouses  shipcube operatein UAE?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently operates one state-of-the-art warehouse across the UAE.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "024",
    "Question": "What are the Shipcube's Fulfillment Available Services for Direct to Customer Orders?",
    "Answer": "Direct-to-Consumer (DTC) Fulfillment allows brands to sell directly to end consumers, bypassing traditional retail channels. This model provides greater control over brand image and about while potentially increasing profit margins.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "025",
    "Question": "What are the Shipcube's Fulfillment Available Services for Business to Business Orders?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube helps you build long-term trust and relationships by offering flexible pricing models and providing comprehensive solutions to simplify complex fulfillment processes across a wide range of services.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "026",
    "Question": "What are the Shipcube's Fulfillment Available Services for Amazon FBA ?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube manages the storage, packaging, and shipping of products for Amazon sellers, ensuring that their items meet all requirements to qualify for Amazon Prime eligibility.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "027",
    "Question": "What does an Account Manager at ShipCube provide?",
    "Answer": "A dedicated Account Manager provides personalized support to maintain and strengthen client relationships, ensuring smooth communication and efficient service delivery.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "028",
    "Question": "What is Real-Time Inventory?",
    "Answer": "Real-time inventory management provides instant visibility of stock levels, enabling efficient and accurate supply chain operations.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "029",
    "Question": "What is Kitting and Assembly?",
    "Answer": "Kitting and Assembly streamline the consolidation of multiple items into ready-to-ship packages, saving time and costs while ensuring accurate integration and high-quality final products.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "030",
    "Question": "Can i track my order?",
    "Answer": "Yes, you can easily track your order in real time through ShipCube's tracking system for complete visibility and updates at every delivery stage.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "031",
    "Question": "What is 3PL (Third-Party Logistics)?",
    "Answer": "A 3PL (Third-Party Logistics) provider plays a crucial role in supply chain management by handling key logistics functions such as warehousing,fulfillment, and transportation on behalf of businesses.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "032",
    "Question": "What are Strategic Warehousing Facilities",
    "Answer": "Strategic warehousing facilities act as key hubs in the supply chain, improving logistics efficiency, inventory management, and distribution performance across multiple regions.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "033",
    "Question": "What are the Logistics Hub Management Centers at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "Logistics Hub Management Centers at ShipCube serve as core facilities that oversee and coordinate all supply chain operations, ensuring efficient movement, storage, and distribution of goods across global networks.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "034",
    "Question": "How can we connect with ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "Simply integrate your online store with ShipCube to get started on the path toward better fulfillment operations and enhanced customer satisfaction.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "035",
    "Question": "How can I get Smart Warehousing with ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "By using data analytics and predictive analysis, ShipCube recommends the optimal quality and SKUs to be stored at its fulfillment centers, ensuring efficient inventory management and faster order processing.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "036",
    "Question": "What is the process of Order Preprocessing?",
    "Answer": "At ShipCube, our fulfillment centers automatically begin processing as soon as a customer places an order on your store, ensuring quick and accurate order fulfillment.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "037",
    "Question": "What about fast delivery?",
    "Answer": "All orders are shipped the same day to ensure quick and reliable delivery to your customers.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "038",
    "Question": "Who are your partners?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube partners with leading global companies such as Softeon, Logiwa, Shopify, Flexport, DHL, FedEx Express, UPS, CVS Pharmacy, Hashcart, Bellavita, and many more, ensuring seamless logistics and fulfillment operations worldwide.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "039",
    "Question": "How do the forward-looking challenges of Technology Integration,",
    "Answer": "Real-time data and integrated systems enable informed, compliant decisions by linking technology, visibility, and compliance—creating sustainable long-term competitive advantages in eCommerce.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "040",
    "Question": "In how many countries does ShipCube deliver products?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube, as a third-party logistics (3PL) and fulfillment company, delivers products globally through partnerships with major international carriers such as DHL, FedEx, and UPS, covering over 220 countries and territories worldwide.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "041",
    "Question": "What vehicle platforms does ShipCube use for delivery?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube uses a range of vehicle platforms for delivery, including trucks, cargo vans, air freight, and sea freight carriers, ensuring fast and reliable transportation across local and international routes.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "042",
    "Question": "What vehicle platforms does ShipCube use for international delivery?",
    "Answer": "For international delivery, ShipCube uses air freight, sea freight, and cargo transport services through global partners like DHL, FedEx, and UPS, ensuring fast, secure, and reliable cross-border shipping.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "043",
    "Question": "How does ShipCube handle returns?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube handles returns through an efficient and structured process that includes inspection, sorting, and categorizing returned goods for restocking, refurbishment, recycling, or disposal. The company ensures accurate quality control, clear return policies, and prompt processing to maintain high customer satisfaction.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "044",
    "Question": "What is ShipCube’s WMS?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's Warehouse Management System (WMS) is an advanced platform that enhances warehouse efficiency by offering real-time inventory visibility, optimized space utilization, accurate order fulfillment, efficient order routing, labor management optimization, and regulatory compliance, ensuring seamless and streamlined warehouse operations.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "045",
    "Question": "How is ShipCube preparing its logistics systems for the future of e-commerce?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube is preparing its logistics systems for the future of e-commerce by investing in automation, AI-driven analytics, and advanced supply chain technology. It is enhancing warehouse automation, route optimization, and real-time tracking systems to improve speed and accuracy.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "046",
    "Question": "How do shipcube structured return processes improve customer satisfaction?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's structured return process improves customer satisfaction by ensuring quick, easy, and transparent returns. Customers can easily initiate returns, track their status, and receive fast refunds or replacements. This builds trust, reduces frustration",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "047",
    "Question": "How does ShipCube ensure order accuracy and timely fulfillment?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube ensures order accuracy and timely fulfillment through its automated Warehouse Management System (WMS), which manages inventory in real time, reduces human error, and optimizes picking and packing. Additionally",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "048",
    "Question": "What steps does ShipCube take to maintain quality control during returns?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube maintains quality control during returns by conducting thorough product inspections, verifying product condition against return policies, and using its WMS tracking system to record each step of the return process. This ensures only eligible, undamaged, and authentic items are restocked or refunded efficiently.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "049",
    "Question": "What does ShipCube’s WMS ensure regulatory compliance and data security?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's WMS ensures compliance and data security through encryption, access controls, and regular audits, following GDPR and global standards to protect customer and shipment data.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "050",
    "Question": "What is ShipCube’s main vision or mission for e-commerce brands?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's main vision is to let e-commerce brands focus on growth while it manages their supply chain and fulfillment. Its mission is to provide reliable, efficient, and technology-driven warehousing and logistics services.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "051",
    "Question": "What does ShipCube ensure customer satisfaction across multiple regions?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube ensures customer satisfaction through advanced technology, efficient operations, and regional warehouses in the U.S., UAE, for faster, reliable fulfillment.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "052",
    "Question": "What does ShipCube’s inclusion in Fulfill.com’s Top 50 signify about its performance",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's inclusion in Fulfill.com's Top 50 US 3PL Companies signifies its strong performance, reliability, and leadership in providing efficient, customer-focused, and innovative logistics solutions.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "053",
    "Question": "What recognition has ShipCube received in 2025?",
    "Answer": "In 2025, ShipCube was recognized by Fulfill.com as one of the Top 50 US 3PL Companies, highlighting its excellence in logistics and commitment to delivering top-tier e-commerce fulfillment solutions.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "054",
    "Question": "What factors contributed to ShipCube’s recognition as a leading 3PL provider?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's recognition as a leading 3PL provider is due to its rapid growth, advanced technology integration, reliable fulfillment solutions, global reach, and strong focus on customer satisfaction and operational excellence.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "055",
    "Question": "What makes ShipCube stand out in the competitive 3PL industry?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube stands out in the competitive 3PL industry through its cutting-edge technology, efficient global operations, data-driven fulfillment solutions, and strong commitment to accuracy",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "056",
    "Question": "What is the WMS ?",
    "Answer": "A WMS (Warehouse Management System) is the strategic planning software that manages inventory levels, stock.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "057",
    "Question": "What is the WES?",
    "Answer": "A WES (Warehouse Execution System) is the real-time tactical layer that automates and optimizes the physical workflow on the warehouse floor (picking, sorting, etc.)",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "058",
    "Question": "What is 10 Core Ways Warehouse Management Systems Drive Value?",
    "Answer": "The ten core ways WMS drives value include: Real-Time Inventory Visibility, Order Accuracy, Optimized Space Utilization, Efficient Order Routing, Labor Management, Regulatory Compliance, Streamlined Returns Management, Accurate Quality Control, Minimized Return Costs, and Enhanced Customer Trust.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "059",
    "Question": "What is ShipCube’s current rating on Google?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently holds a 5.0 rating on Google Reviews.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "060",
    "Question": "What is ShipCube’s current followers on LinkedIn?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently has 557 followers on LinkedIn.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "061",
    "Question": "What is the warehouse space did ShipCube have when it was founded?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube was founded in 2020 with just 3,000 sq. ft. of warehouse space in New Jersey.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "062",
    "Question": "What is the warehouse space does ShipCube currently have?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently operates with 500,000 sq. ft. of warehouse space.",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "063",
    "Question": "What is the current company size of ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently has a company size of 51–200 employees.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "064",
    "Question": "What is the associate members does ShipCube have?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube currently has 44 associate members.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "065",
    "Question": "What is ShipCube’s primary headquarters located?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's primary headquarters is located at 700 Ramona Ave, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania 19120, United States.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "066",
    "Question": "Could you please share the percentage of ShipCube’s growth rate for the year 2025?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube recorded an impressive growth rate of 1,314% from 2021 to 2025.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "067",
    "Question": "What is ShipCube’s rank among the fastest-growing companies in America 2025?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube is ranked #292 on this year's Inc. 5000 list of the fastest-growing companies in America.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "068",
    "Question": "How much warehouse space does ShipCube have in the UAE?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube has 20,000 sq. ft. of warehouse space in the UAE",
    "Departments": "Warehouse"
  },
  {
    "id": "069",
    "Question": "Is ShipCube listed on any stock exchange?",
    "Answer": "No — ShipCube LLC is not listed on any stock exchange.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "070",
    "Question": "What is the founding year or age of ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube is 2 years, 4 months, and 4 days old.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "071",
    "Question": "What is the business category or industry classification of ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube is a Limited Liability Company (LLC), which means it operates as a company limited by shares.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "072",
    "Question": "What is the business sub category of shipcube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube is registered as a non-government company operating in the logistics and fulfillment sector.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "073",
    "Question": "What is the authorised share capital of ShipCube Services Private Limited?",
    "Answer": "The authorised share capital of ShipCube Services Private Limited is ₹1,500,000 (Rupees Fifteen Lakhs only).",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "074",
    "Question": "What is the authorised Paid-up Share Capital of Shipcube Services Private Limited?",
    "Answer": "The authorised share capital of ShipCube Services Private Limited is ₹ 100,000.00",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "075",
    "Question": "Has ShipCube received any external funding or venture capital investment ?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube is currently an unfunded company, operating without any external or venture capital investment.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "076",
    "Question": "How many competitors does ShipCube have in the global fulfillment and logistics industry?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube has 130 active competitors in the global fulfillment and logistics industry.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "077",
    "Question": "Could you please provide the names of ShipCube’s competitors in the global fulfillment and logistics industry?",
    "Answer": "The top competitors of ShipCube include companies such as Shiprocket, ShipBob, and Locus.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "078",
    "Question": "How quickly can I start using ShipCube, and what does the onboarding process involve?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube offers a fast and smooth onboarding process, typically completed within a few weeks. It includes initial data setup, integration with your eCommerce platforms.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "079",
    "Question": "Could you please let me know the top export HS code for ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The top export HS codes for ShipCube are 33059090, 33059019, 33051090, and 83061000.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "080",
    "Question": "Could you please share the top export ports used by ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube primarily exports through the following ports: Nhava Sheva Sea Port; Hyderabad Air Cargo.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "081",
    "Question": "Could you please let me know the top export country for ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's top export country is the United States.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "082",
    "Question": "who the top export buyers of ShipCube are?",
    "Answer": "ShipCube's top export buyers include: Sabinsa Europe GmbH, Van Caem Hair Care B.V, Katyani Enterprises Private Limited, L'Oréal Australia Accounts",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "083",
    "Question": "How to find a trade shipments of shipcube?",
    "Answer": "You can explore detailed shipment records and Shipcube Llc export import data through Eximpedia's real-time trade insights platform, which provides access to shipment dates, quantities, ports, and product details.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "084",
    "Question": "Can you provide a similar buyers like shipcube?",
    "Answer": "Yes, Eximpedia offers a directory of buyers with similar trade patterns to Shipcube Llc. Use advanced filters to identify competitors, Shipcube Llc importers or partners in the same industry.",
    "Departments": "Logistics"
  },
  {
    "id": "085",
    "Question": "What are the primary import and export of shipcube?",
    "Answer": "Eximpedia's trade data highlights Shipcube Llc's major exports, along with their trade destinations and origins. To know the updated Shipcube Llc trade data, visit our platform.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "086",
    "Question": "Who is shipcube service private limited's key principal?",
    "Answer": "shipcube service private limited's key principal is Hooner Baweja.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "087",
    "Question": "What is the CIN of Shipcube Services Private Limited?",
    "Answer": "The CIN of Shipcube Services Private Limited is U63030TN2022PTC156483.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "088",
    "Question": "When was Shipcube Services Private Limited incorporated?",
    "Answer": "Shipcube Services Private Limited was incorporated on 09 November 2022.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "089",
    "Question": "Who are the current directors of Shipcube Services Private Limited?",
    "Answer": "The current directors of Shipcube Services Private Limited are Lakshman Kumar Shukla,Hooner Baweja,Meenu Baweja",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "090",
    "Question": "What is the primary industry of Shipcube Services Private Limited?",
    "Answer": "The primary industry of Shipcube Services Private Limited is Transportation.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "091",
    "Question": "What is the capital structure of Shipcube Services Private Limited?",
    "Answer": "The authorized capital of Shipcube Services Private Limited is ₹1.50 M, and the paid-up capital is ₹0.10 M.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "092",
    "Question": "Could you please let me know if customized unboxing is available at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "Yes, ShipCube offers customized unboxing services.",
    "Departments": "About"
  },
  {
    "id": "093",
    "Question": "What is the monthly handling price charged by ShipCube for managing and processing inventory?",
    "Answer": "The monthly handling price charged by ShipCube for managing and processing inventory is $0.30 per unit.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "094",
    "Question": "What are the material fees charged by ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The material fee charged by ShipCube is $11.67 per pallet.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "095",
    "Question": "What are the inbound charges at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The inbound charges at ShipCube are $2.25 per box.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "096",
    "Question": "What are the pick charges at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The pick charge at ShipCube is $0.25 per unit.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "097",
    "Question": "What are the IN/OUT and labeling charges at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The IN/OUT and labeling charges at ShipCube are $2.25 per case.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "098",
    "Question": "What are the charges of a 40' container at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The cost of a 40' container at ShipCube is $441.67 per container, reflecting our commitment to providing efficient and cost-effective logistics solutions.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "099",
    "Question": "What are the charges of a 20' container at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The cost of a 20' container at ShipCube is $316.67 per container, reflecting our commitment to providing efficient and cost-effective logistics solutions.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "100",
    "Question": "Could you please tell me the cost of pallet unloading at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "At ShipCube, the pallet unloading cost is $13.67 per pallet.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "Question": "Could you please share the cost of account setup at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The account setup cost at ShipCube is $100.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "Question": "What are the WMS (Warehouse Management System) charges at ShipCube?",
    "Answer": "The WMS (Warehouse Management System) charges at ShipCube are $15 per month.",
    "Departments": "Finance",
    "RequiresLogin": true
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "Question": "What are your service payment terms?",
    "Answer": "Our payment terms offer a standard window, ranging from Due Upon Receipt to a maximum of Net 30 Days.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "Question": "What are your shipping payment terms?",
    "Answer": "We kindly request payment upon receipt of the invoice and, for your convenience, can accommodate terms up to Net 7 Days.",
    "Departments": "Finance"
  }
]